<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Riddey on It’s not just a whiteboard, it’s a canvas for innovation | Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/</link><description>Recent content in Riddey on It’s not just a whiteboard, it’s a canvas for innovation | Riddey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://riddey.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/contact/</guid><description> Drop us a Line Let us know what we can do to get you Riddey
info@riddey.com Your Name* Your e-mail address* Message I've read and accepted the Terms and Conditions Send message Contact us Terms &amp; Conditions Privacy Policy Pricing Follow us LinkedIn X (former Twitter) Facebook Newsletter Get access to all the latest trends and updates
Subscribe Start using Riddey today!</description></item><item><title>Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/features/</guid><description>Features Discover our plans and choose the best option. Canvas Operations When using our platform, you'll have access to a wide range of basic canvas operations that make your creative journey effortless. You can express your ideas through drawing, correct or modify them with erasing, effortlessly select and transform elements, add text to convey your message effectively, and connect various components seamlessly using connectors. These fundamental tools are designed to provide you with a versatile and intuitive canvas experience, ensuring that you can bring your vision to life with ease.</description></item><item><title>Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/meet-the-team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/meet-the-team/</guid><description>Vision Statement At Riddey, our vision is to transform collaboration and creativity by providing a dynamic and intuitive online whiteboard experience. We aspire to be the go-to platform that empowers individuals, teams, and organizations worldwide to connect, ideate, and innovate seamlessly, transcending geographical boundaries. Through continuous innovation and user-centric design, we aim to foster a world where ideas flow effortlessly and creativity knows no limits. Mission Statement Our mission at Riddey is to deliver a superior online whiteboarding solution that enhances productivity, communication and ideation.</description></item><item><title>Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/pricing/</guid><description>Choose your package Discover our plans and choose the best option.
Month Year Lifetime Basic Plan Unlimited snap boards Up to 3 Permanent boards Basic Export Free shapes Up to 4 participants per board Free Sign up Most Popular Premium Plan Everything in basic plus Unlimited permanent boards Access control Premium shapes Up to 20 board participants Up to 3 project folders Advanced Export $8 Pay once. Enjoy forever! Try it now Platinum plan Everything in premium plus Unlimited project folders Premium shapes for all Platinum badge Priority email support $10 Pay once.</description></item><item><title>Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/product-map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/product-map/</guid><description>Product Roadmap Q1 2024 Editor More interactive shapes This will include rounded rectangle, polygon, callouts, and sticky notes Sequence diagram Operations that have been carried out will now be shown in an interactive diagram Frames Users will be able to input shapes within other shapes Integrations Github Login Q2 2024 Editor Templates Users will have template options to choose from Automatic diagram organization Diagrams will be automatically organized for user convenience Integrations Slack Zoom System Dark mode Q3 2024 Editor Mindmaps Users can brainstorm using our mindmap option</description></item><item><title>Why is it Hard to Draw with a Mouse and What Can You Do About It?</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/why-it-is-hard-to-draw-with-a-mouse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/why-it-is-hard-to-draw-with-a-mouse/</guid><description>Why is it Hard to Draw with a Mouse and What Can You Do About It? Were you a big-time whiteboard user before the work-from-home era? And now, do you just talk and gesture in Zoom meetings instead of using an online whiteboard? If so, you are not alone—many don&amp;rsquo;t even bother because they feel it is too difficult. Have you ever wondered why?
To start things off, here is a personal story some might relate to.</description></item><item><title>We have just released our private beta</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/changes/v1.0-beta-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/changes/v1.0-beta-release-notes/</guid><description>v1.0-beta is out We have been working very hard since the last release to deliver as much value as possible. So I proudly announce that our private beta is up and running. You need an invite to sign up, so if you don&amp;rsquo;t have but want one:
Request Invite In this release, we delivered the following:
Rebranding Our original intention was to create a whiteboard that makes people&amp;rsquo;s life easier by its superior UI.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://riddey.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy Last updated: 11/10/2023 This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://riddey.com (the "Site"). Personal Information We Collect When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Use</title><link>https://riddey.com/terms-of-use/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 18:48:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/terms-of-use/</guid><description>Terms of Use Last updated on 11/18/2023 Introduction Welcome to Coolboard LLC, incorporated in State of Texas (registration number 804743688) ("Riddey", "Company", "we", "our", "us")! These Terms and Conditions of Use govern your use of our web pages located at https://riddey.com and our software operated by Coolboard LLC that performs functions of a visual collaboration space. Our Privacy Policy also governs your use of our website and explains how we collect, safeguard and disclose information that results from your use of our web pages.</description></item></channel></rss>