<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on It’s not just a whiteboard, it’s a canvas for innovation | Riddey</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on It’s not just a whiteboard, it’s a canvas for innovation | Riddey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://riddey.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unlocking the benefits of Online Collaboration</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/unlocking-the-benefits-of-online-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/unlocking-the-benefits-of-online-collaboration/</guid><description>Unlocking the Benefits of Online Collaboration in Both Remote and In-Office Work Environments In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced and interconnected world, collaboration is the cornerstone of success for businesses and organizations. With the rise of technology, online collaboration has become a game-changer, transforming the way teams work together. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re working remotely or in the office, online collaboration tools and practices offer numerous advantages that can boost productivity, innovation, and overall efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Riddey, your online canvas of Innovation!</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/riddey-set-go-introducing-riddey-your-online-canvas-of-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/riddey-set-go-introducing-riddey-your-online-canvas-of-innovation/</guid><description>Riddey.Set.Go - Introducing Riddey, your online canvas of Innovation! With technology at the forefront of all work functionality, effective collaboration is more crucial than ever. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re excited to introduce Riddey, your new go-to online virtual whiteboard. With Riddey, you can empower your teams to collaborate from anywhere in the world, foster creativity, and streamline your creative processes, all while enjoying an array of innovative features designed to make your work easier and more productive.</description></item><item><title>Why is it Hard to Draw with a Mouse and What Can You Do About It?</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/why-it-is-hard-to-draw-with-a-mouse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/articles/why-it-is-hard-to-draw-with-a-mouse/</guid><description>Were you a big-time whiteboard user before the work-from-home era? And now, do you just talk and gesture in Zoom meetings instead of using an online whiteboard? If so, you are not alone—many don&amp;rsquo;t even bother because they feel it is too difficult. Have you ever wondered why?
To start things off, here is a personal story some might relate to. After the pandemic hit, I had a video meeting with one of my friends.</description></item><item><title>We have just released our private beta</title><link>https://riddey.com/blog/changes/v1.0-beta-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://riddey.com/blog/changes/v1.0-beta-release-notes/</guid><description>v1.0-beta is out We have been working very hard since the last release to deliver as much value as possible. So I proudly announce that our private beta is up and running. You need an invite to sign up, so if you don&amp;rsquo;t have but want one:
Request Invite In this release, we delivered the following:
Rebranding Our original intention was to create a whiteboard that makes people&amp;rsquo;s life easier by its superior UI.</description></item></channel></rss>